Yunus Emre Kepenek

Full Stack Software Engineer based in Türkiye, İzmir with more than 2 years of professional experience with a focus on building engaging & accessible applications with TypeScript, React, Next.js, NestJS, SvelteKit and more.

yunus.emre.kepenek@outlook.com +90 552 461 32 03 github.com/yuunsgit linkedin.com/in/yekepenek yunusemre.dev

Relevant Experience

Full Stack Engineer · Radity

Sep 2023 — Present

Zürich, Switzerland

- Build, style, and ship more than 5 high-quality insurance portals for a
 diverse array of clients including THREE Insurance by Berkshire
 Hathaway, using technologies such as React, Next.js, Nest.js, Redux,
 JavaScript, TypeScript, Material UI, Figma, and more.
- Work alongside product & project managers, designers, and other engineers to transform creative concepts into refined digital experiences at an agile cadence.
- Emphasize Swiss-quality standards in every stage of development, ensuring reliability, efficiency, and precision in the final digital solutions.

Freelance Software Engineer · Tipsiti

Aug 2024 — Present

San Francisco, CA

- Maintained a dynamic travel curation platform using modern web technologies such as Next.js, TypeScript, and Zustand, focusing on showcasing local places, products, and experiences across various cities.
- Contributed to the implementation of responsive and interactive UI components for grid and map views, enhancing user experience in exploring curated travel content.

Full Stack Engineer · DT Cloud

Jan 2023 — Sep 2023

Antalya, Türkiye

- Developed high-end cloud services, laaS and PaaS software solutions using technologies such as React, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Chakra UI, Redux, Figma, and more.
- Implemented client-requested features, resulting in a 30% boost in user satisfaction and retention.
- Contributed to the development of end-to-end tests with Cypress, leading to a 20% decrease in the occurrence of errors and system failures.

Education

Software Engineering · Ankara Science University

GPA: 3.5/4 Ankara, Türkiye

Relevant coursework:

- Web Design and Programming
- Advanced Web Design with React

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES2015+), TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Java, Python, SQL

Libraries & Frameworks

React, Node.js, Next.js, Nest.js, Svelte, SvelteKit, Astro, Tailwind CSS, Framer Motion, Redux, Zustand, Playwright, Express

Tools & Platforms

PostgreSQL, Git, GitHub, GitLab, Azure, Redis, Vercel, Heroku, WordPress, Docker, Webpack, Figma

Organizations

Sinbad DigiBox · Founder

Ankara Science University

Provided invaluable guidance and mentorship in web development technologies to CS students.

Personal Projects

ABÜ Tanıtım · University Promo Site

Self Shelf · Library App **Conversions** · PDF Editor

Certificates

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate

Received training from Meta, creator of React, upon completing 9 courses successfully.

Languages

English · Fluent

Turkish · Native